

Bruno Jose Biasotti

Date of birth: 17/06/1992 Nationality: Argentinian

Gender: Male

CONTACT

Sarmiento, n° 152 5507 Mendoza, Argentina (Home)

elbiazzo025@gmail.com

(+54) 92612631274

https://github.com/ BrunoBiasotti/Portfolio

in https://www.linkedin.com/in/bruno-biasotti-080033158/

+5492612631274 (Whatsapp)



ABOUT ME

I am an Electronic Engineer with focus on Data Analytics and Python/SQL programming. After three years working as a Field Inspector for the Oil&Gas industry, in real-time measurement and visualization, I realized how much I love to work with data. Data is our ally to answer questions, solve problems and make good, data-driven decisions to improve.

I wish to expand further on my digital skills in an evolving, challenging project/industry

WORK EXPERIENCE

03/02/2019 - 01/04/2022 - Las Heras, Santa Cruz, Argentina

Field Inspector

AESA

Inspection tasks, operation, quality, safety and finances

Development of KPI's in Python and Microsoft SQL and visualization through PowerBI to find any inconsistencies in day-to-day operations, data quality and finances.

KPI successfully implemented:

- Data availability (improved from ~90% to ~97% availability for a month - 400+ data-points, real-time processing, transmitting data 24/7)
- Data reliability (improved from ~85% to ~98% reliability for a month - 8000+ data-points, batch processing, transmitting data 24/7)
- Finances (to discover, inform and evaluate the payment of nontransmitting data-points for both: real-time and batchprocessing data)

02/04/2018 - 20/11/2018 - Mendoza, Argentina

SCADA programmer

Freelance

SCADA programming and implementation of a fertilizer production plant

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

15/03/2010 - 13/04/2018 - Mendoza, Argentina

Electronic Engineer with orientation in telecommunications

Universidad de Mendoza

Tech skills in automation, electronics, programming

Soft skills in analytical thinking, results-oriented, project management

Address Av. Boulogne Sur Mer 683, Mendoza, Argentina | **Website** <u>h</u> ttps://um.edu.ar/ | **Field of study** Electronics and automation | **Fin al grade** 8.75

Data Analyst

Google / Coursera

Tech skills: SQL, R, Tableau

Soft skills: Data cleaning, Analytical thought, create engaging visuals, make data-driven suggestions **Field of study** Inter-disciplinary programmes and qualifications involving Information and Communication Technologies (ICTs)

LANGUAGE SKILLS

MOTHER TONGUE(S): Spanish

OTHER LANGUAGE(S):

English

Listening B2	Reading B2	Spoken production B2	Spoken interaction B2	Writing B2
German				
Listening A2	Reading A2	Spoken production A1	Spoken interaction A1	Writing A2

DIGITAL SKILLS

My Digital Skills

Data Analytics

Data Analysis (Python) / Database Management (SQL) / R / Excel Tableau Power Bi **General IT skills**

Linux / Git / Microsoft Office / SQL / Python / VBA (Basic)



ARGENTINA

Universidad de Mendoza Facultad de Ingeniería

El Rector de la Universidad y el Decano de la Facultad

Bruno Jose Biasotti

junio de 1992 en Santa Erux « Rep Angentina

ha terminado el Plan de Estudios de la Carrera de Ingeniería y cumplido todos los requisitos legales y reglamentarios. Por tanto: de acuerdo a las atribuciones que les confiere la ley, le expiden el presente título de

Ingeniero en Electrónica con Orientación Telecomunicaciones

en la Ciudad de Mendoxa, República Argentina, a

del año dos mil clieccocho,

Mater (AREJANDRO MANNO

Mu And Almodo (designs

dias del mes de abril

Registrado en Folio 33 del Libro de Grados Nº: 11

Fecha de Egreso: 13-04-18D.1.Dtd.1. Nº 36.926.002.



Graurheindorfer Str. 157 D-53117 Bonn

Tel.: +49 (0)228 501 664 Fax.: +49 (0)228 501 229 zabservice@kmk.org http://www.kmk.org/zab http://anabin.kmk.org

Reg.-Nr.: L2022/311610

Bonn, 26.08.2022

Zeugnisbewertung für ausländische Hochschulqualifikationen

Die Bewertung erfolgt unter der Voraussetzung der Echtheit und Richtigkeit des Zeugnisses.

Herr Bruno José Biasotti, geboren am 17.06.1992 in Santa Cruz, weist den folgenden ausländischen Hochschulabschluss nach:

Abschluss: Ingeniero en Electrónica con Orientación

Telecomunicaciones

Wörtl. Übersetzung: Elektronikingenieur mit Schwerpunkt

Telekommunikation

Studiengang: Ingeniería en Electrónica (Elektronikingenieurwesen)

Fachrichtung: Telecomunicaciones (Telekommunikation)

Institution: Universidad de Mendoza

Ort: Mendoza
Staat: Argentinien
Dauer: 5 Jahre
Ausstellungsdatum: 13.04.2018

Bewertung

Der ausländische Abschluss entspricht einem deutschen Hochschulabschluss. Er ist vom Niveau her zwischen der Bachelor- und der Masterebene einzuordnen.

i.A.

Konference





Google Data Analytics Certificate

ISSUED TO

Bruno Biasotti



Issued on: 26 MAY 2022 | Issued by: Coursera Verify: https://www.credly.com/go/sHQFVi6v